<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | Shishir Shakya</title>
    <link>https://ShishirShakya.github.io/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://ShishirShakya.github.io/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© `2022` Shishir Shakya</copyright>
    <image>
      <url>https://ShishirShakya.github.io/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>https://ShishirShakya.github.io/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ShishirShakya.github.io/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ShishirShakya.github.io/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am an Assistant Professor of Economics in the Department of Economics at the Shippensburg University of Pennsylvania.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am an applied economist specializing in three unique research domains: healthcare provider labor/licensing markets, the opioid epidemic, and, recently, entrepreneurship. My broader goal is to understand the health care market in the USA, various consequences of health policies, and labor market regulation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use various applied econometric, spatial, policy evaluation techniques, and and supplement my empirical knowledge with the practice of technology-driven methods such as data-scrapping, big data, predictive, and causal machine learning approaches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have published in numerous peer-reviewed academic journals, including the &lt;em&gt;World Development&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Annals of Regional Science&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Energy Economics&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am teaching Microeconomics in summer 2022 and Principles of Economics in Fall 2022. In addition, I have taught Regional Economics, Economic Analysis of Big Data, Principles of Economics, Principles of Macroeconomics, Managerial Economics, Business Data Visualization, and Elementary Business &amp;amp; Economic Statistics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For any questions about my research or other scholarly activities, please contact me by email &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sshakya@ship.edu&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;sshakya@ship.edu&lt;/a&gt;. You can also reach me on Twitter &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/econshishir&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;@econshishir&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
